Milne School; Records ua659
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Crimson and White Senior News, 1931 October 16-1941 May 24; 13; 0.4 cubic ft. 198 Digital Files
  - Senior News, 1931 October 23 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1931 October 30 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1931 November 6 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1931 November 13 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1931 November 20 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1931 December 4 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1931 December 11 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 January 8 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 January 15 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 January 15 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 January 22 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 February 19 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 February 26 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 March 4 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 March 11 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 March 18 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 April 8 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 April 15 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 April 22 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 April 29 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 May 6 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 May 13 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 May 19 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 May 27 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 October 7 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 October 14 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 October 21 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 October 28 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 November 4 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 November 11 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 November 23 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 December 2 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 December 16 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1932 December 21 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 January 13 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 January 20 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 January 27 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 February 10 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 February 17 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 February 24 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 March 3 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 March 10 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 March 17 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 March 24 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 March 31 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 April 7 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 April 28 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 May 5 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 May 18 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 May 26 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 June 2 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 October 6 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 October 13 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 October 20 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 October 27 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 November 3 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 November 10 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 November 17 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 November 24 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 December 8 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1933 December 15 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 1)
  - Senior News, 1934 January 12 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 January 19 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 January 26 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 February 16 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 February 23 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 March 2 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 March 9 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 March 16 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 March 22 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 March 23 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 April 13 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 April 20 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 April 27 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 May 4 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 May 11 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 May 17 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 May 25 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 June 1 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 October 5 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 October 12 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 October 26 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 November 2 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 November 9 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 November 16 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 November 23 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 December 7 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1934 December 14 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1935 January 11 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1935 January 18 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1935 February 8 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1935 February 15 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1935 March 1 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1935 March 8 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1935 March 15 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1935 March 22 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1935 March 29 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1935 April 5 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1935 April 12 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1935 April 18 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1935 May 3 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1935 May 10 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1935 May 31 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1935 October 18 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1935 October 25 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1935 November 1 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1935 November 8 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1935 November 15 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1935 November 22 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1935 November 27 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1935 December 6 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1935 December 13 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1935 December 20 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 2)
  - Senior News, 1936 January 10 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1936 January 17 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1936 January 24 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1936 February 14 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1936 February 21 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1936 February 28 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1936 March 6 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1936 March 27 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1936 April 3 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1936 April 9 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1936 May 1 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1936 May 8 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1936 May 22 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1936 May 29 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1936 June 5 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1936 October 3 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1936 October 16 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1936 October 23 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1936 October 30 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1936 November 6 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1936 November 13 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1936 November 20 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1936 December 4 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1936 December 11 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1936 December 18 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 January 8 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 January 15 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 January 22 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 January 29 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 February 12 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 February 19 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 February 26 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 March 6 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 March 12 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 March 19 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 April 9 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 April 16 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 April 23 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 April 30 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 May 7 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 May 14 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 May 28 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 October 8 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 October 15 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 October 22 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 October 29 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 November 5 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 November 19 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 December 3 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 December 10 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1937 December 17 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 3)
  - Senior News, 1938 January 7 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1938 January 14 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1938 January 21 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1938 January 28 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1938 February 18 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1938 February 25 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1938 March 4 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1938 March 11 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1938 March 18 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1938 March 25 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1938 April 1 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1938 April 8 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1938 April 29 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1938 May 6 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1938 May 13 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1938 May 20 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1938 May 27 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1938 October 7 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1938 October 21 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1938 October 28 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1938 November 4 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1938 November 11 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1938 December 2 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1938 December 9 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1938 December 16 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1939 January 6 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 4)
  - Senior News, 1939 January 13 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 January 20 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 February 10 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 February 17 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 February 24 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 March 3 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 March 17 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 April 5 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 April 21 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 April 28 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 May 5 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 May 12 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 May 19 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 May 26 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 June 2 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 October 6 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 October 13 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 October 20 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 October 27 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 November 3 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 November 10 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 November 13 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 November 17 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 November 22 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 December 1 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 December 8 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1939 December 15 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 5)
  - Senior News, 1940 January 5 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 January 12 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 January 19 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 January 26 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 February 16 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 February 23 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 March 1 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 March 8 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 April 5 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 April 12 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 April 19 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 April 26 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 May 3 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 May 10 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 May 17 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 June 6 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 October 4 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 October 11 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 October 18 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 October 25 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 November 1 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 November 8 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 November 20 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 November 29 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 December 6 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 December 13 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1940 December 20 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1941 January 10 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1941 January 17 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1941 February 7 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1941 February 14 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1941 February 21 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1941 February 28 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1941 March 7 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1941 March 14 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1941 March 21 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1941 March 28 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1941 April 9 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1941 April 25 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1941 May 2 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1941 May 9 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
  - Senior News, 1941 May 24 (Box 39 (13-Crimson and White Senior News), Folder 6)
- Crimson and White Junior News, 1931 October 16-1941 May 24; 14; 0.4 cubic ft. 215 Digital Files
  Series is made up of the Crimson and White: Junior Newspaper dating from 1931-1941.
  - Junior News, 1931 October 2 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1931 October 16 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1931 October 23 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1931 October 30 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1931 November 6 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1931 November 13 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1931 November 20 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1931 December 4 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1931 December 11 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 January 8 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 January 15 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 January 15 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 January 22 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 February 19 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)
  - Junior News, 1932 February 26 (Box 40 (14-Crimson and White Junior News), Folder 1)